
0.01:Hello kid! It's a good day huhhhh?
0.01:Oh wait! What's in your hand?
0.01:An apron?! I remember this handcraft!
0.01:it's my mom's!!!
0.01:How did you get this apron?
0.01:Huh?!
0.01:So...
0.01:She asked you to bring this to me...
0.01:But she didn't tell you where am I...
0.01:..............
0.01:I'm sorry. My mom should make you feel very confusing, right?
0.01:Anyway, thank you very much.
0.01:I have to go now.