Hey you!
Sorry again for the trouble that my mom made.
Actually…
I might be the one who should be responsible for this case...
There are only me and my mom in our family. My dad was dead since I was young.
So, it’s my mom who work really hard to find the money and keep us alive.
That was a really hard time..
I wanted my mom to have more comfortable life.
So, when I was 25, I decide to leave this house and work at the butcher shop……
