
0.01:Oh my! Hello!
0.01:What are you doing in the wood?
0.01:Oh! You are from Heritia, aren’t you?
0.01:My name is Christine.
0.01:May I ask you a favor?
0.01:Can you help me send this letter to someone who’s living in Heritia?
0.01:I met him on a rainy day.
0.01:We had a great time back then.
0.01:But I don’t know his name...
0.01:Instead, he left me with the beautiful dagger and said that he will be back again someday.
0.01:If you found him, please tell him that I’m still waiting for him.
0.01:Thank you! You’re so kind!