
0.01:Something is wrong!
0.01:I was inside the mine until there was some earthquake!
0.01:I was so panic! So I ran out from the mine as fast as I can…
0.01:The only thing I can grab along the way is this pickaxe.
0.01:Some parts of the mine are inaccessible, but luckily the light still works.
0.01:Hey kid! Can you do me a favor? 
0.01:I need you to find me some fresh foods.
0.01:Some chicken wings, maybe?
0.01:Otherwise I may not able to continue my digging jobs…
0.01:Here take this last coin.