LB : I see...
LB : Looks like my dog found his new friend somewhere far away, that’s why I can’t find him…
LB : Anyway, thanks for help me finding my dog!
LB : Because of you, me and my dog we’re together.
LB : I promise I will never lose him again.
D : Bark!
HD : Bark!
LB : Also, look what we’ve found along the way home!
LB : I’m not sure what to do with it…
LB : Please take this as my thanks. 
*Receive a gem*
